Finding Aid for Christina V. Pacosz diaries and publications, 1899-2011.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Works published online
  - "Letter from Haiti to the Dead," http://www.poetryrepairs.com/v07/035.html 2007.
  - "Can You Whitewash the Spirit?" Published in The Temple, Tsunami, Inc., 2001 Greatest Hits 1975-2001 Pudding House 2003 Poetry Repairs; "Weston Bend State Park, Weston, Missouri," January, 2003 Prairie Poets Award, first prize winner, Jane's Stories. Publication on web page, www.janespress.org
  - "Letter from Haiti to the Dead" Featured on The Hyper Texts as the Spotlight Poet in Spring of 2007 http://www.thehypertexts.com
  - "A New Broom Sweeps Clean," "The Mother of Violence," "When I Was" http://www.umbrellajournal.com/spring2007/poetry/ChristinaPacosz.html Issue 2, Spring 2007.
  - "The Map Is Not the Territory," Pemmican, Issue number 33, http://www.pemmicanpress.com, Spring 2007.
  - "Beneath the Heart of America Bridge in Kansas City, Missouri" Volume 7.11:121 http://www.poetryrepairs.com/v07/121.html
  - "In the Garden," "Summer Is Fraying," "Unspeakable," http://www.northeastartskc.org/down0307/anti_war.htm DownGo Sun, March 2007.
  - "Some Winded, Wild Beast," "Death Is a Door," "To Be a Fish with Blind Eyes," from Some Winded, Wild Beast, Black and Red, Detroit, 1985 appeared on line in kritya Vol II1/Part V (November 2007) Editor's Choice section http://www.kritya.in/0306/En/editors_choice.html
  - "Counting Monarchs in Kansas City" http://qarrtsiluni.com/2007/11/26/counting-monarchs-in-kansas-city/ qarrtsiluni online literary magazine
  - "One River," www.umbrellajournal.com/winter2007/cold/Christina Pacosz.html Issue 4, Winter/2007
  - "At the Center," short story, http://www.thanalonline.com/Issues/06/ehome.htm Thanal Online, Volume 2. Issue 2, December 2007.
  - Essay about poet Genevieve Taggard in March 2, 2008 issue of Umbrella Journal http://www.umbrellajournal.com/spring2008/poetry/ChristinaPacosz.html
  - "The Third, the Youngest Sister Explains Her Success" reprinted from Mississippi Mud date uncertain as copy lost in fire, but sometime in the 1980s http://www.umbrellajournal.com/spring2008/milestones/ChristinaPacosz.html
  - Christina Pacosz on thehypertexts.com, http://www.thehypertexts.com/Christina%20Pacosz%20Poet%20Poetry%20Picture%20Bio.htm